https://github.com/btomer/WiFiManager


Note from btomer

This is a fork of tzapu's WiFiManager that supports me-no-dev's ESPAsyncWebServer. This is needed because ESP8266WebServer (which is used by the original version of WiFiManager) and ESPAsyncWebServer don't compile together, so you couldn't use them both in your project.

To use this fork all you have to do is replace the original WiFiManager.h and WiFiManager.cpp files (under <Arduino_IDE_dir>/libraries/WiFiManager/) with the matching files in this repository, and add the following define before including WiFiManager.h:

// NOTE: This requires btomer's fork of the WiFiManager library (https://github.com/btomer/WiFiManager)

#define WIFI_MANAGER_USE_ASYNC_WEB_SERVER
#include <WiFiManager.h>

If you do not define WIFI_MANAGER_USE_ASYNC_WEB_SERVER then WiFiManager will work with ESP8266WebServer.
